Guide to the Mix Collection 1970-2001 (Bulk 1987-2001) MSS 143
© 2012 Fales Library and Special Collections
- SERIES XVIII: Other Festivals
    - United States - New York City - New York Underground Film Festival - program guides, Indiewire article, 1998-2000 (Box 32, Folder 1419)
    - United States - New York City - Thessaloniki USA Film Festival - program guide, 1999 (Box 32, Folder 1420)
    - United States - New York City - W.O.W. Women's Film and Video Festival - schedule, 1996 (Box 32, Folder 1421)
    - United States - Orlando - Central Florida Film and Video Festival - program guide, flyer, 1998 (Box 32, Folder 1422)
    - United States - Philadelphia - Philadelphia International Gay and Lesbian Film Festival - program guide, 1998 (Box 32, Folder 1423)
    - United States - Phoenix - Phoenix Lesbian and Gay Film Festival - program guide, 1999 (Box 32, Folder 1414)
    - United States - Portland - Sensory Perceptions: Portland Gay and Lesbian Film Festival - program guide, 1998 (Box 32, Folder 1425)
    - United States - Princeton - Queer Articulations: Princeton Lesbian, Gay and Bisexual Film Festival - program guide, 1993 (Box 32, Folder 1426)
    - United States - Rochester - ImageOut: Rochester Lesbian and Gay Film and Video Festival - program guide, 1998 (Box 32, Folder 1427)
    - United States - St. Paul - Film in the Cities: Lesbian, Gay, Bisexual and Transgender Film Festival - program guide, 1992 (Box 32, Folder 1428)
    - United States - San Diego - San Diego Latino Film Festival - program guide, 1999 (Box 32, Folder 1429)
    - United States - San Francisco - Film Arts Festival - program guide, 1987 (Box 32, Folder 1431)
    - United States - San Francisco - Frameline: San Francisco International Lesbian and Gay Film Festival - program guide, press release, 1988-1992 (Box 32, Folder 1432)
    - United States - San Francisco - Frameline: San Francisco International Lesbian and Gay Film Festival - program guide, directory of queer film festivals, press releases, call for entries, 1993-1994 (Box 32, Folder 1434)
    - United States - San Francisco - Frameline: San Francisco International Lesbian and Gay Film Festival - press clippings, correspondence, distribution catalogs, invites, flyers, festival statements, guest accreditation, holiday card, 1994-1996 (Box 32, Folder 1435)
    - United States - San Francisco - Frameline: San Francisco International Lesbian and Gay Film Festival - program guides, 1998-1999 (Box 32, Folder 1436)
    - United States - San Francisco - Jewish Film Festival - program guides, 1994-1995 (Box 32, Folder 1437)
    - United States - San Francisco - Jewish Film Festival - program guides, 1997-1998 (Box 32, Folder 1438)
    - United States - Seattle - Seattle Lesbian and Gay Film Festival - program guides, 1998-1999 (Box 32, Folder 1439)
    - United States - Washington, D.C. - Reel Affirmations: Washington, D.C.'s International Gay and Lesbian Film Festival - program guides, 1998, 2000 (Box 32, Folder 1440)
- SERIES XIX: Miscellaneous
  This series contains miscellaneous files found in the Mix Collection, divided into 11 subseries.
  - Subseries A: Non-Mix Press/Promotion/Posters (see also Oversize series)
    - The Advocate - June 6, 2000 (Box 33, Folder 1441)
    - Amsterdam News - Essex Hemphill obituary, 1995 (Box 33, Folder 1444)
    - CNYPG newsletter - Shu Lea Cheang article, 1995 (Box 33, Folder 1446)
    - Crucial Anatomy #4 - Stephen Kent Jusick zine, 1994 (Box 33, Folder 1447)
    - Filmmaker Magazine, vol. 7.3, 1999 (Box 33, Folder 1448)
    - HX, vol. 4.39, 1994 (Box 33, Folder 1449)
    - HX, vol. 7.33, 1997 (Box 33, Folder 1450)
    - Images in the Dark - promotional material, 1994 (Box 33, Folder 1451)
    - Impulse #9, 1994 (Box 33, Folder 1452)
    - The Independent: Film and Video Monthly, Nov. 1999 and Mar. 2000, 1999, 2000 (Box 33, Folder 1453)
    - Index, Feb./Mar. 2000 (Box 33, Folder 1454)
    - Index, Sep./Oct. 2000 (Box 33, Folder 1455)
    - Living Magazine, vol. 2:8, 1994 (Box 33, Folder 1459)
    - Manhunt Magazine, vol 1:8, 1994 (Box 33, Folder 1460)
    - New York Times - "33 Receive MacArthur Fellowships", 1992 (Box 33, Folder 1461)
    - New York Times - "Still Arguing the Value of Warhol's Estate", 1992 (Box 33, Folder 1462)
    - New Yorker - Nov. 10, 1997 (Box 33, Folder 1464)
    - Next Magazine, vol. 2:10, 1994 (Box 33, Folder 1465)
    - Next Magazine, vol. 2:15, 1994 (Box 33, Folder 1466)
    - Next Magazine, vol. 4:6, 1996 (Box 33, Folder 1467)
    - Out and About, vol. 3:6, 1994 (Box 33, Folder 1468)
    - Paper, Oct. 1995 (Box 33, Folder 1469)
    - Popcorn, issue 5, 1993 (Box 33, Folder 1471)
    - Prometheus, winter 1995 (Box 33, Folder 1473)
    - Real Screen Magazine, Apr. 2000 (Box 33, Folder 1474)
    - Release Print, Aug. 1997, Oct. 1997 (Box 33, Folder 1475)
    - Release Print, May 2000 issue and correspondence (Box 33, Folder 1475a.)
    - RES Magazine, vol. 2:2, 1999 (Box 33, Folder 1476)
    - Simon Says, vol. 4:1, 1999 (Box 33, Folder 1479)
    - Steam: A Quarterly Journal for Men, vol. 1:1, 1993 (Box 33, Folder 1480)
    - Time Out New York, issue 50, 1997 (Box 33, Folder 1482)
    - Video Magazine - VCR/Camcorders Buyers Guide, 1990 (Box 33, Folder 1484)
    - unknown - "The Filmmaker's Cooperative: Still Present, Still Muddling Through", n.d. (Box 33, Folder 1490)
    - unknown - "Top CDC official says gay teens need help", n.d. (Box 33, Folder 1491)
    - misc. writings - Annie Sprinkle, "101 Uses for Sex", n.d. (Box 33, Folder 1492)
    - misc. writings - Moira Sweeney, "Towards a New Erotica", 1989 (Box 33, Folder 1493)
    - misc. writings - Jerry Tartaglia, "For the Love of Man: The Poetic Visions of James Broughton" (part II), 1987 (Box 33, Folder 1494)
    - Flyers/posters - Films - Advocacy Video Conference and Screenings, 1993 (Box 33, Folder 1495)
    - Flyers/posters - Films - Anthology Film Archives - The Myth of Our Power: Films by Filipino Women, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 1496)
    - Flyers/posters - Films - Anthology Film Archives - Maya Deren postcard, 1990 (Box 33, Folder 1497)
    - Flyers/posters - Films - Bianchi, Sergio, A Causa Secreta, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 1498)
    - Flyers/posters - Films - Bociurkiw, Marusia, Bodies in Trouble, 1997 (Box 33, Folder 1499)
    - Flyers/posters - Films - Camarda, George, The Olive Tree, 1999 (Box 33, Folder 1501)
    - Flyers/posters - Films - Collective for Living Cinema, Barbara Hammer and Su Friedrich postcards, 1990 (Box 33, Folder 1502)
    - Flyers/posters - Films - The Cooler, Dawg, 1994 (Box 33, Folder 1503)
    - Flyers/posters - Films - Dubowski, Sandi, Trembling Before G-d, 2001 (Box 33, Folder 1504)
    - Flyers/posters - Films - Genuine Ladies film screening, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 1505)
    - Flyers/posters - Films - Goss, John, Video Data Bank postcard, 1989 (Box 33, Folder 1506)
    - Flyers/posters - Films - Hammer, Barbara, "Lesbian Erotica by...", 1987 (Box 33, Folder 1507)
    - Flyers/posters - Films - Langlois, Denis, L'Escorte, 1996 (Box 33, Folder 1508)
    - Flyers/posters - Films - Lesbian and Gay Youth Project, Framed Youth (Box 33, Folder 1509)
    - Flyers/posters - Films - New York State Council of the Arts, "Set in Motion", 1994 (Box 33, Folder 1510)
    - Flyers/posters - Films - Summers, A.K., World Without Femmes, Part III postcard, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 1511)
    - Flyers/posters - Films - von Praunheim, Rosa, "Neues von Rosa von Praunheim" flyer, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 1512)
    - Flyers/posters - Films - Webo-Holegrain Films, Caspar Stracke/Bill Morrison poster, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 1513)
    - Flyers/posters - Films - White Columns, Video Hang Out flyer, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 1514)
    - Flyers/posters - Galleries/performances - Exit Art/The First World postcard, 1993 (Box 33, Folder 1515)
    - Flyers/posters - Galleries/performances - HOME - Homosexuals on Parade Dance Co. flyer, 1989 (Box 33, Folder 1516)
    - Flyers/posters - Galleries/performances - Jack Tilton Gallery, Patty Chang exhibit flyer, 1999 (Box 33, Folder 1517)
    - Flyers/posters - Galleries/performances - Koussevitzky Gallery, Susan Schiller, "Cheap Tricks" exhibit flyer, 1988 (Box 33, Folder 1518)
    - Flyers/posters - Galleries/performances - L.A. Galerie, Hiroshi Sunairi exhibit flyer, 2000 (Box 33, Folder 1519)
    - Flyers/posters - Galleries/performances - Leslie/Lohman Gay Art Foundation postcards, 1993 (Box 33, Folder 1520)
    - Flyers/posters - Galleries/performances - P.S. 122, Carmelita Tropicana, "Milk of Amnesia" flyer, 1994 (Box 33, Folder 1521)
    - Flyers/posters - Galleries/performances - Twilo, Soigne exhibit flyer, 1994 (Box 33, Folder 1522)
    - Flyers/posters - Magazines - Pepgirlz #2 postcard, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 1523)
    - Flyers/posters - Magazines - Princess Magazine flyer, 1996 (Box 33, Folder 1524)
    - Flyers/posters - Gay bars - Candy Bar and Grill flyer, 1996 (Box 33, Folder 1525)
    - Flyers/posters - Gay bars - Miracle Club flyer, 1989 (Box 33, Folder 1526)
    - Flyers/posters - Gay bars - misc., 1992 (Box 33, Folder 1527)
    - Flyers/posters - Real estate - Downtown New York brochures, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 1528)
    - Flyers/posters - Film/printing - Color Scan postcard, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 1529)
    - Flyers/posters - Film/printing - Corinne Offset Printing flyer, 1987 (Box 33, Folder 1530)
    - Flyers/posters - Film/printing - Rafik flyer, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 1531)
    - Flyers/posters - Misc. - Designs, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 1532)
  - Subseries B: Catalogs/Programs (non-festival) (see also Oversize series)
    - Catalogs - Berlin Film Festival: American Independents and Features Abroad, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 1533)
    - Catalogs - Berlin Film Festival: New Cinema from Japan, 1999 (Box 33, Folder 1534)
    - Catalogs - The British Council: British Films Catalogue, 1999 (Box 33, Folder 1535)
    - Catalogs - British Film Institute: Gay and Lesbian Film Catalogue, 1993-1994 (Box 33, Folder 1536)
    - Catalogs - Buzzwords Independent Television Service, 1998 (Box 33, Folder 1537)
    - Catalogs - California Newsreel: Library of African Cinema, 2000 (Box 33, Folder 1538)
    - Catalogs - Cowboy Booking International, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 1539)
    - Catalogs - The Digital Directory: Art and Technology Resources in New York State, 1999 (Box 33, Folder 1540)
    - Catalogs - Electronic Arts Intermix: Video Catalog, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 1541)
    - Catalogs - Electronic Arts Intermix: New Artists, New Tapes, 1995 (Box 33, Folder 1542)
    - Catalogs - Entry: A guide to photographic competitions and juried exhibitions, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 1543)
    - Catalogs - Film/Video Arts: Celebrating 30 Years, 1999 (Box 33, Folder 1544)
    - Catalogs - Filmfriends equipment catalog, 1999 (Box 33, Folder 1545)
    - Catalogs - First Run/Icarus Films, 1999 (Box 33, Folder 1546)
    - Catalogs - Frameline Distribution film and video catalogs, 1999-2000 (Box 33, Folder 1547)
    - Catalogs - Free Speech TV: Human Rights Advocacy Kit, 1999 (Box 33, Folder 1548)
    - Catalogs - Haworth Press Catalog, 1994 (Box 33, Folder 1549)
    - Catalogs - Hong Kong Independent Short Film and Video Awards, 1997 (Box 33, Folder 1550)
    - Catalogs - Hong Kong Independent Short Film and Video catalog, 1999 (Box 33, Folder 1551)
    - Catalogs - Independent Feature Project: 9th Annual Independent Feature Film Market, 1987 (Box 33, Folder 1552)
    - Catalogs - Insound Anniversary Catalog, 2000 (Box 33, Folder 1553)
    - Catalogs - Japanese Experimental Film and Video 1955-1994 (Box 34, Folder 1554)
    - Catalogs - London Filmmakers Co-Op: Light Years: A Twenty Year Celebration, 1986 (Box 34, Folder 1555)
    - Catalogs - London Filmmakers Co-Op Catalogue, 1996 (Box 34, Folder 1556)
    - Catalogs - National Association of Artists' Organizations: A Document and Directory of the NAAO, 1998 (Box 34, Folder 1557)
    - Catalogs - October Films/Good Machine:MiFED 1998 (Box 34, Folder 1558)
    - Catalogs - Paper Tiger Television, 1997/1998 (Box 34, Folder 1559)
    - Catalogs - P.O.V.: American Ideals, American Realities, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 1560)
    - Catalogs - Strand Releasing, 1998/1999 (Box 34, Folder 1561)
    - Catalogs - Third World Newsreel, 1997 (Box 34, Folder 1562)
    - Catalogs - Video Data Bank: Gay and Lesbian Titles, 1995 (Box 34, Folder 1563)
    - Catalogs - Video Data Bank, 2000 (Box 34, Folder 1564)
    - Catalogs - Women Make Movies Catalogue of Films and Videos supplement, 1990/1991 (Box 34, Folder 1565)
    - Catalogs - Women Make Movies catalogs, 1994, 1999 (Box 34, Folder 1566)
    - Catalogs - Zeitgeist Films Catalogue, 1992 (Box 34, Folder 1567)
    - Film programs - American Museum of the Moving Image - Jack Smith retrospective press release, 1997 (Box 34, Folder 1569)
    - Film programs - Anthology Film Archives - Charles Henri Ford program listing, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 1570)
    - Film programs - Anthology Film Archives - Fluxfest program guide, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 1571)
    - Film programs - Anthology Film Archives - Howard Guttenplan program listing, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 1572)
    - Film programs - Anthology Film Archives program guide, July-August 2000 (Box 34, Folder 1573)
    - Film programs - Baltimore Museum of Art, 1990 (Box 34, Folder 1575)
    - Film programs - Banff Centre for the Arts program guides, 1995 (Box 34, Folder 1576)
    - Film programs - British Film Institute film programs - Andy Warhol, Dada, Heroic Times (Box 34, Folder 1577)
    - Film programs - Brooklyn Academy of Music - BAMcinematek program guide, July-Sept. 2000 (Box 34, Folder 1578)
    - Film programs - Brooklyn Museum film/video program guides, 1993-1994 (Box 34, Folder 1579)
    - Film programs - Centre Georges Pompidou - Cinema Experimental et d'Artistes program listing, 1995 (Box 34, Folder 1580)
    - Film programs - Cinematheque program guide, spring 1992 (Box 34, Folder 1581)
    - Film programs - Collective for Living Cinema - Gay and lesbian film schedule, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 1582)
    - Film programs - Guggenheim Film - Fever in the Archive exhibition guide, 2000 (Box 34, Folder 1583)
    - Film programs - Jesus' Son press kit, 1999 (Box 34, Folder 1584)
    - Film programs - The Kitchen - The Exploding Valentine program guide, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 1585)
    - Film programs - London Electronic Arts brochures, 1997 (Box 34, Folder 1586)
    - Film programs - London Filmmakers Co-Op program guide, November 1987 (Box 34, Folder 1587)
    - Film programs - Lux Centre schedule, fall 1997 (Box 34, Folder 1588)
    - Film programs - Museum of Modern Art - Cineprobe: Roger Jacoby program info, 1987 (Box 34, Folder 1590)
    - Film programs - Museum of Modern Art - Cineprobe: Yann Beauvais and Marguerite Paris program info, 1988-89 (Box 34, Folder 1591)
    - Film programs - Museum of Modern Art film programs, 2000 (Box 34, Folder 1592)
    - Film programs - Pioneer Theater schedule, March 2000 (Box 34, Folder 1593)
    - Film programs - San Francisco Cinematheque schedule, winter 1994 (Box 34, Folder 1596)
    - Film programs - Scratch Projection program listing, June 21, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 1597)
    - Misc. catalogs - A Gift for Me, 2000 (Box 34, Folder 1602)
    - Misc. catalogs - Best Impressions, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 1603)
    - Misc. catalogs - Bookspan, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 1604)
    - Misc. catalogs - Eddie Bauer Home, 2000 (Box 34, Folder 1605)
    - Misc. catalogs - Wigstock '94, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 1606)
  - Subseries C: Jim Hubbard
    - Personal correspondence - holiday cards, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 1607)
    - Personal correspondence - Jim Hubbard and Nelson Gonzalez, 1992 (Box 34, Folder 1608)
    - Personal correspondence - Projections/Teddy Awards, 1995 (Box 34, Folder 1609)
    - Personal correspondence - James Broughton to Phil Willkie, 1992 (Box 34, Folder 1610)
    - Personal correspondence - Phil Willkie to Jim Hubbard, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 1611)
    - Personal correspondence - New York State Division of Housing and Community Renewal, 1990 (Box 34, Folder 1611a.)
    - Personal correspondence - USA/Club Marketing, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 1611b.)
    - Personal expenses - Travel Horizons invoice for Berlin flight, 1990 (Box 34, Folder 1612)
    - Itinerary for Europe trip, 1990 (Box 34, Folder 1613)
    - Flyer - Jim Hubbard and Nelson Gonzalez' 10th anniversary party, 1992 (Box 34, Folder 1614)
    - Resume, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 1615)
    - Special guest faculty contract, SF Arts Institute, 1985 (Box 34, Folder 1616)
    - NYSCA - supplemental film production application for Elegy in the Streets, 1986 (Box 34, Folder 1617)
  - Subseries D: Sarah Schulman (see also Oversize series)
    - OutWeek - "Is the NEA Good for Gay Art?", 1990 (Box 34, Folder 1620)
    - Photo: Sarah Schulman, Raoul Tenazas, Mary Filippo, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 1621)
  - Subseries E: Shari Frilot
    - Party flyers, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 1622)
    - Personal correspondence, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 1623)
    - Personal expenses, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 1624)
    - Resume, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 1625)
    - Grant application for Jocelyn Taylor - Bodily Functions, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 1626)
  - Subseries F: Karim Ainouz/Latino Collaborative
    - Application - American Film Institute National Video Festival, 1992 (Box 34, Folder 1627)
    - Application - Harvestworks Artists-in-Residency, 1992 (Box 34, Folder 1628)
    - Correspondence - personal, 1992 (Box 34, Folder 1629)
    - Correspondence - grant foundations, 1992 (Box 34, Folder 1630)
    - Correspondence - London Lesbian and Gay Film Festival, 1992 (Box 34, Folder 1631)
    - Correspondence - Raul Ferrara-Balanquet, 1992 (Box 34, Folder 1632)
    - Expenses - AT+T billing change form, 1992 (Box 34, Folder 1633)
    - Expenses - Chemical Bank, 1992 (Box 34, Folder 1634)
    - Expenses - Renewal lease form, 1993 (Box 34, Folder 1635)
    - Expenses - misc. receipts, 1992 (Box 34, Folder 1636)
    - Films - Subtitle outline for Seams, 1992 (Box 34, Folder 1637)
    - Flyers - Brazilian museums, 1992 (Box 34, Folder 1638)
    - Flyers - Copabanana, 1992 (Box 34, Folder 1639)
    - Flyers - Imants - Fundacio Joan Miro, 1992 (Box 34, Folder 1640)
    - Miscellany - Solo Man catalog, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 1641)
    - Miscellany - World of Video membership card, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 1642)
    - Miscellany - envelopes, 1992 (Box 34, Folder 1643)
    - Latino Collaborative - Administrative files, correspondence, invoices (inc. also Chelsea Piers and Silver Screen Studios proposal summaries), 1992 (Box 34, Folder 1644)
    - Latino Collaborative - Administrative files, correspondence, invoices, 1992 (Box 34, Folder 1645)
  - Subseries G: Rajendra Roy
    - Guggenheim files, 1997-1998 (Box 34, Folder 1646)
    - Love or Story film project - shooting notes, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 1647)
    - "Ra Gender" - History and manifesto, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 1648)
    - Siegessaule Extra: Teddy '98 - Rajendra Roy mention, 1998 (Box 34, Folder 1649)
  - Subseries H: Jack Waters/Allied Productions/Naked Eye Cinema
    - Jack Waters - Resume, 1993 (Box 34, Folder 1650)
    - Jack Waters - Grants/fundraising - Art Matters, Inc., 1988 (Box 34, Folder 1651)
    - Jack Waters - Grants/fundraising - Creative Time, Inc., 1989 (Box 34, Folder 1652)
    - Jack Waters - Grants/fundraising - Empire State Craft Alliance, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 1653)
    - Jack Waters - Grants/fundraising - Materials for the Arts, 1990 (Box 34, Folder 1654)
    - Jack Waters - Grants/fundraising - New York Hall of Science, 1990 (Box 34, Folder 1655)
    - Jack Waters - Grants/fundraising - The Pollock-Krasner Foundation, 1990 (Box 34, Folder 1656)
    - Allied Productions - Expenses - Activity report for Winter and Spring newsletters, 1992 (Box 34, Folder 1657)
    - Allied Productions - Expenses - MCI card, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 1658)
    - Allied Productions - Expenses - Telephone bill, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 1659)
    - Allied Productions - Statements - Call for contributions, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 1660)
    - Allied Productions - Statements - Call for submissions (Flique), 1992 (Box 34, Folder 1661)
    - Allied Productions - Grants/fundraising - Department of Cultural Affairs contract, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 1662)
    - Allied Productions - Grants/fundraising - Department of Cultural Affairs contract and final report figures, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 1663)
    - Allied Productions - Grants/fundraising - Grants pending, 1989 (Box 34, Folder 1664)
    - Allied Productions - Grants/fundraising - National Endowment for the Arts, 1984-1985 (Box 34, Folder 1665)
    - Allied Productions - Grants/fundraising - National Endowment for the Arts - application and final report, 1988-1989 (Box 34, Folder 1666)
    - Allied Productions - Grants/fundraising - National Endowment for the Arts - InterArts application and final report + New York Foundation of the Arts Artist Fellowship guidelines, 1986-1989 (Box 35, Folder 1667)
    - Allied Productions - Grants/fundraising - National Endowment for the Arts - InterArts grant application, 1989 (Box 35, Folder 1668)
    - Allied Productions - Grants/fundraising - National Endowment for the Arts - InterArts grant application, 1990/1991 (Box 35, Folder 1669)
    - Allied Productions - Grants/fundraising - National Endowment for the Arts - dance project application, 1988-1991 (Box 35, Folder 1670)
    - Allied Productions - Grants/fundraising - National Endowment for the Arts - grant application, 1991/1992 (Box 35, Folder 1671)
    - Allied Productions - Grants/fundraising - New York State Council of the Arts - ABC No Rio final report, 1989/1990 (Box 35, Folder 1672)
    - Allied Productions - Grants/fundraising - New York State Council of the Arts - ABC No Rio final report, 1990 (Box 35, Folder 1673)
    - Allied Productions - Grants/fundraising - New York State Council of the Arts - ABC No Rio grant application, 1989 (Box 35, Folder 1674)
    - Allied Productions - Grants/fundraising - New York State Council of the Arts - correspondence re: Antiutopia, 1988-1989 (Box 35, Folder 1675)
    - Allied Productions - Grants/fundraising - New York State Council of the Arts - cultural services contract, 1990 (Box 35, Folder 1676)
    - Allied Productions - Grants/fundraising - New York State Council of the Arts - final report form, 1989/1990 (Box 35, Folder 1677)
    - Allied Productions - Grants/fundraising - New York State Council of the Arts - final report form for ABC No Rio repairs, 1990 (Box 35, Folder 1678)
    - Allied Productions - Grants/fundraising - New York State Council of the Arts - final report form and cultural services contract, 1990/1991 (Box 35, Folder 1679)
    - Allied Productions - Grants/fundraising - New York State Council of the Arts - grant application, 1989 (Box 35, Folder 1680)
    - Allied Productions - Grants/fundraising - New York State Council of the Arts - project descriptions, 1989 (Box 35, Folder 1681)
    - Allied Productions - Grants/fundraising - New York State Council of the Arts - miscellaneous administrative files, 1989 (Box 35, Folder 1682)
    - Naked Eye Cinema - Carl George correspondence to filmmakers, 1987 (Box 35, Folder 1683)
    - Naked Eye Cinema - Call for queer films, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 1684)
    - Naked Eye Cinema - Catalog, 1987 (Box 35, Folder 1685)
  - Subseries I: Anthology Film Archives
    - Correspondence and other info re: gay filmmakers (Gregory Markopoulos, Stefan Hayn), 1993-1995 (Box 35, Folder 1686)
    - February 1994 ticket sales figures (Box 35, Folder 1687)
    - Miscellany, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 1688)
  - Subseries J: Miscellaneous/Undated Files (see also Oversize series)
    - Business cards and menus, ?-1997 (Box 35, Folder 1689)
    - G.L. Towers Syndicates Reinsurance form, `989 (Box 35, Folder 1691)
    - Notice for available office space, 1996 (Box 35, Folder 1692)
    - Queer film bibliography, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 1693)
    - Unknown correspondence (Box 35, Folder 1694)